BLAM
JULY 15TH (THURS) 12:42 PM
SWIP
Breakdown, Breakdown
(Listen up)
(Listen)
Breakdown, Breakdown
(3, 2, 1) Let's Go!
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
Shining Justice begins to sprout
Brand-new bed town
Will we meet? Let's find out
Feeling the sea breeze from the cape
through the tunnel to the tower
We wander into the alley,
drawn to each other
A shadow melts into our hearts
But the golden spirits
shine a light to protect us
Let the voice of love
take you higher
Let the gathering forces
overcome time itself
1999 Bizarre Summer
Our courage keeps the town in bloom
Great Days
JULY 15TH (THURS) 1:39 PM
EPISODE 33
JULY 15TH (THURS), PART 3
M PREFECTURE S CITY,
MISSING PERSONS
JULY 15TH (THURS) 12:55 PM
JULY 15TH (THURS) 12:47 PM
KOICHI HIROSE
THUD
JULY 15TH (THURS) 2:21 PM
TERUNOSUKE MIYAMOTO
JULY 15TH (THURS) 1:20 PM
FOOM
KOICHI HIROSE
JOSUKE HIGASHIKATA
MORIOH LIBRARY
JULY 15TH (THURS) 4:10 PM
JULY 15TH (THURS) 4:30 PM
JULY 15TH (THURS) 4:52 PM
EPISODE 34
JULY 15TH (THURS), PART 4